Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Why do you have
to go so far from the city
to take care
of some old geezer?
We really need the money.
Did you forget
about the eviction notice?
She's getting way more than what
you make in a month waitressing.
Says Miss No Job.
I'm trying. You know
I'm gonna help out when I can.
Mm-hm. Sure.
So, how does a waitress
get a car like this, Maria?
- Mm-hm.
- James Miller.
Ew. I thought
you didn't like him.
Well, I like his car.
- You stole it?
- No, I... I borrowed it.
- So, what do you...
- It's nice to keep.
Is that him?
- I think so.
- I told you we were running late.
- No sweater.
- Let's get out.
Come on,
come on, come on.
Thanks.
- Miss Cherry Holly?
- Yes, nice to meet you.
I'm Dwayne from the Hallawells.
Thank you for picking me up.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Here you go.
Thanks. I can take it myself.
Okay. Thank you.
We love you.
We'll see you next week,
sis, okay?
- Call us when you get there, please, okay?
- Seriously.
Of course, of course.
Love you. Okay,
drive safe, please.
- I'll try.
- And get that car back to that man.
Oh, can I sit up front?
- As you wish, miss.
- Okay, thank you.
Thanks.
Can we stop for something
cold to drink?
My treat.
Sorry, there's nothing
along the road.
You like it?
It was my grandma's.
We're here.
Wait here a moment.
Miss Hallawell is ready
to see you now.
No, please.
I'll take care of it.
Please sit.
It's so nice to meet you,
Miss Hallawell.
Thank you.
I truly appreciate this
opportunity, Miss Hallawell.
I really need this job.
Only 21, correct?
Excuse me?
My age?
- Yes, people sometimes...
- Apart from the hospital,
do you have any other experience
caring for the elderly?
No.
I expect you to take
excellent care of my father.
You can count on me.
Due to a skin condition,
my father cannot be exposed
to strong light.
Only use the gas lamps.
The drapes must remain closed
even during the night.
Wait.
Come.
Father.
This nurse
will be caring for you
while I'm away.
Dwayne goes into town
every Thursday.
To get father's blood supply
from donors at the hospital.
How can I reach you
if there's an emergency?
Dwayne will go into town,
and communicate with me.
There are no telephones
in this house.
Dwayne!
She will eat in the kitchen.
I'm sorry. I...
Sorry.
It's really good.
Thank you.
While I am away,
the house
is your responsibility.
And the girl, too.
Good morning, Mr. Hallawell.
Dwayne.
- Miss?
- Call me Cherry.
Can you lower the heater?
We don't have a heater.
Whose piano is that?
It's Mr. Phillip's.
He used to play.
Why? Do you play?
No. I dance.
Cherry.
You shouldn't touch that.
Oops.
I'm going into town.
Do you need anything?
Yes, please.
Love letter?
Maybe.
It's to my friends.
Okay, I'll see you later.
See ya.
Sorry.
Dwayne told me
you used to play the piano.
I would love to learn
how to play an instrument.
I'm a great dancer, though.
At least I think I am.
Cherry.
Cherry, wake up.
Come on.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're a good caregiver.
Almost as good as me.
You must have had
a very caring mother.
Tell me about your family.
We were on a boat
escaping from our island.
There was a storm.
The last thing I remember
is the boat turning over.
How do you end up here?
I don't know.
Miss Naomi
kind of adopted me.
I'm also an orphan.
I always dreamed
a family would adopt me.
No one ever did.
Where do you live now?
I've lived with my friends
my entire life.
They're like my sisters.
Do you remember anything
about your real family?
My grandma.
It's less every day.
Hey...
Do you know what I do
when I get down?
No, what?
I get down.
This was Miss Naomi's
ballet studio years ago.
What a wonderful space.
Wait, I'm gonna
show you something.
I love that record.
I dance to it
with my sisters all the time.
- You should join me.
- No, I'll just watch.
Why not? It's fun.
Come here. Just dance.
I'll teach you.
Just follow my moves.
There you go.
Just keep rolling your arms,
and move your hips.
That's it, you've got it.
What's wrong?
We should stop.
Were you able to rest,
Mr. Hallawell?
- How's Mr. Phillip?
- All right.
Are there any other Hallawells?
It's only Mr. Phillip
and Miss Naomi.
Miss Naomi always wanted to have
children, but she wasn't able to.
So what are you gonna do
when you finish your job here?
Go home,
back to the hospital
and take some dance classes.
What about you?
Me?
- Stay here.
- Forever?
Don't you have any dreams?
Dreams? About what?
Life, travel.
Having your own family.
I was raised by the old servant Louie.
He taught me a lot.
He taught me
that it doesn't matter
where you are going
or what you do in life.
Your fate's already written.
I believe it's true.
Do you know where
the family photos are?
I just really
love old pictures.
You were so cute.
That was taken
the day I came here.
It's the only picture of me.
Was there ever
another kid in the house?
No.
Is that Naomi?
Yes, and her tutu.
Stunning.
That's Mr. Phillip's
sister Violet.
Louie told me she was outcast
on the family.
Look, that's Mr. Phillip.
He was a grand man.
A highly respected psychic.
Mommy.
Good morning, Phillip.
Dwayne.
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah.
I'm going to the forest.
- I would like to come with.
- You wanna come with me?
Let me just grab my coat.
It's special here.
Can I try?
- Try what?
- Shooting.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
This rifle is very powerful.
I can handle it.
Hold it steady.
You got it.
I told you I could do it.
- That was beginner's luck.
- Maybe I'm just a natural.
Like you are with dancing.
Nah.
I mean it.
You can really move.
So can you.
Nice, I guess.
Let's go.
This can cause trouble, Cherry.
They'll leave
first thing in the morning.
Why are you here?
It was Maria's idea.
But you were the first one
in the car, baby.
I'm really sorry, Cherry.
We just wanted to see you.
So, did you and Dwayne...
- get it on?
- Maria!
Come.
Jeez, it's so hot in here.
Goodnight, Phillip.
♪ Saturday nights
And Sunday morning
♪ Stumbling home
When the day is dawning
♪ I wanna do it all over again
Here.
Not today.
Ugh. More for us then.
Here.
Oh, come on, Dwayne.
- Don't be such a drag. Play with us.
- Keep it down, Maria.
Whatever.
♪ Everything will be all right
Okay.
Come here.
Dwayne does not want to play.
Come on, Dwayne.
- It's really easy.
- I'll explain.
Are you paying attention,
Dwayney-Dwayne?
Okay.
Each one of us is gonna take a
piece of paper from out of this bag.
Whatever comes out...
must be done.
Okay, you go first.
- Who wrote them up?
- Both of us.
You have to do it
with your eyes closed.
Duh!
♪ I'll see you again tonight
♪ Everything will be all right
- What does it say?
- Come on.
Tell us.
Oh, my God.
Okay. You go.
No, you first.
Okay, scaredy-cat.
Read it.
Lick... the floor.
- That's mine.
- Okay, okay. Ready?
Do it, do it.
Ew!
Okay. You go.
Quickly.
What does it say?
Kiss the boy you like the most.
Well, that's easy. I mean,
there's only one boy, right?
I mean, if that's cool
with you, right, Cherry?
♪ ...Sunday morning
♪ Stumbling home
When the day is dawning
♪ I wanna do it
All over again ♪
Bravo!
Oh, gosh.
I need to pee.
Oh, no, no. No, no. It's okay.
I can go by myself.
Oh, where is it?
It's downstairs,
down the hall, to your right.
Downstairs,
Downstairs, down the hall,
to the right.
Maria's taking too long.
I'll go and find her.
What's wrong?
I don't like it here.
Maria! Maria!
Come back! Maria!
Maria! Oh!
Maria! Don't leave me here!
Skank!
Ugh!
She's gone.
Cherry, are you
seeing things again?
Where were you?
In the woods,
looking for Maria.
She split.
I want to leave... now.
It's Maria. Stop.
Stop the car.
Stop the car!
What are you doing?
It's Maria!
Stop! Stop!
Maria!
It's not real.
It's all in my head.
It's not real,
it's all my head!
it's all my head.
It's not real,
It's not...
it's all my head.
It's not real,
It's all in my head.
it's all my head.
No, it is.
Cherry.
Cherry!
No!
Dwayne.
Dwayne!
It's a blade.
Dwayne.
Dwayne!
Dwayne, are you here?
Dwayne.
No! No! No! No!
No!
No! No!
Why are you
all doing this?
Cherry.
Cherry!
Dwayne.
You let it happen.
All of it!
Remember your place.
She is in the forest.
You belong here.
Cherry!
I'm leaving.
Come with me. Come.
I can't.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull